Yeah! We're halfway there!
Our fiftieth card! All right!
los beautyi
Co-di-fi
You can fly away
Okay then
The trade is complete
Wait, hold on just a second
I'm afraid I can't accept this
This isn't a fair trade
You're kidding!
Don't complain after the deal is done!
We gave you three cards, didn't we?
Yeah! What more do you guys want?
Just calm down
That's not what I meant
It's fine for me, but it's unfair to you
It's too skewed in our favor
It feels like you're giving us a free lunch
And I don't like it
Even if we're able to clear the game first
Well, that's the kind of thing that would weigh on me
I have a proposition for you
Choose right or left
And I'll give you whichever card you pick
One of them's worthless
But the other
Is Angel's breath
Yes!
Levy on!
Wait, damn it, no!
Return on!
Masadora
Let's go after them!
Not yet!
First, check the cards in your books
I lost one of the number 80s we were trying to monopolize
And a number 65 as well
Hey, what about you?
I lost numbers 42 and 53
And I lost 29 and 24!
This is bad!
They got me for two of the 85s that we've been hoarding!
All the ones they took were specified slot guards
And they took both types we were monopolizing
Damn!
They must have used risky dice
We're not with them, I promise!
He's right!
They used an item to change our faces!
We can't just stand here, let's find them!
No!
Hey, tell me, is Gen through the bomber?
I... I don't know
Sorry
But he did go like this with his hand and
Blew the head off the guy I was with!
A power that is clearly meant specifically for murder
So he's no stranger to fighting battles, that much is obvious
It would be unwise to try to fight them head on
We have to!
Sir, they took at least five different card types from us!
Just think about it!
They could have completed their collection!
Now list on, card number two
It looks like they still haven't found number two, strip of beach
We're all right for the time being
Our immediate priority is to find the number two card before they can get to it
Well, we still have our exchange voucher for Angel's Breath
It is possible
You're right!
Let's get out there and find it!
Accompany on!
To Sofrabi!
Congratulations! We did it!
The risky dice and levy combination really paid off
We're at 93 types!
No, we used one up to change those guys' faces, remember?
So we're right at 92
But the important thing is that we took the cards they were monopolizing
And for two of the other ones, we're just waiting for someone to use gain on them
The biggest obstacle for us now is number two
Good point, but at least we know that it's somewhere in Sofrabi
Right, then we'll go after 72, 21, and 9, all in that order
And then we'll head to Sofrabi to find number two
For 75, we'll just find someone who has it and take it from them
I think it's time we started thinking
About the three specified slot cards that we each want to keep
And how to spend our 50 billion
Hey, Killua
There's something that's been bugging me lately
Yeah?
There are hundreds of players in this game, aren't there?
But in spite of that, we've been able to turn every item we've obtained into cards
And that's weird, right?
Wait, what do you mean?
You can only convert a card so many times
And even B-rank specified slot types have a 30-card limit
I would have thought that the players here before us would have already collected them, you know?
I guess that's true
But there is one other way you can look at it
Not that many teams here can make real progress
Maybe fewer than 30
Oh, yeah, I get it
See, most of the players don't seem to be all that worried about getting specified slot cards
Best I can tell, they're just struggling to find a way out of the game
It'd suck if you got to Masadora and couldn't find any leave cards there
Sure would
That's why
That's it
What?
If you guys got to Masadora and there weren't any leave cards there, what would you do?
Well, let me think
I'd save up some money and wait until another leave card showed up
Yup
Okay, so then what if you acquired a super rare spell card while you were there waiting?
I guess I would just sell it and buy more spell cards until a leave came in
Really?
Huh?
Because I would definitely save it
Wouldn't it be awful if all the cards you bought ended up being worthless?
If you saved it, maybe you could trade up for a leave, but
Well
Hmm
Need a leave?
You want to go back home?
I think we can help you
Okay, now we've got four specified slot cards for three leaves
Yeah, making a total of 54 types in all
Score!
All right
All of the cards that wouldn't fit in our binders have reverted into items
Looks like we're running out of free slots pretty fast
We should probably organize them
We've got 135 free slots between the three of us
So we should each leave five slots free
How about you keep the spell cards, Killua?
Biski needs a few defensive ones
Hold on
I have to use spell cards?
No way!
Those are far too confusing
Then study!
What the hell?
Okay
Book
So up to this point, we've been deliberately avoiding the other players
But now, there are certain cards we really need
So we'll have to take some risks
Well, I suggest we get all that we can ourselves
And then actively negotiate with other players we meet on the way
That sound good to you?
I'm in
Yeah!
See ya
Wait a second
This card is worthless
It's just a transformed fake
Oh wow, I'm really sorry about that
Here's the real one
You can't trust any of these guys, huh?
We better stay on the defensive
No joke
We're lucky he has that necklace
It certainly comes in handy
Okay, I got a question
This necklace is supposed to be able to remove curses, right?
From spell cards
But not any others
Oh, guess it won't work then
What, you have an idea, Gon?
I was just wondering if maybe a curse was behind the disease those villagers were suffering from
What villagers?
Oh, I remember those guys
The ones who took all your money, right?
I doubt that would work because they're not cards
Right
But still, it might be worth a shot
It's a lot to ask
But will you trust us with your lives?
You gave us everything you had without even the slightest hint of hesitation
Yes, we trust you
It worked!
Thank you all very much
This treasure has been passed down for many generations
Please accept it
It worked!
We got a wild luck Alexandrite!
Heck yeah!
Attention, another player has cast contact on you
Hey, this is Kazu
Could you and I meet in person?
I really have to talk to you
About what?
A team is close to clearing the game
A three-man team led by someone named Genthru
Genthru
Thanks for taking the time to come out, everyone
As I mentioned via contact
Team Genthru is getting very close to completing the game
I just checked the ranking
And they're currently at 96 types
We have to come up with a strategy
And now
I've got a question
Yeah
How exactly do you check the rankings?
Oh, well
Great, you don't even know how to do that
We don't have time to explain the whole game to them
So just cut to the chase, alright?
There's no need to be mean
All of us are here to exchange information
He's right, Asta
You never know
These kids just might have a bit of intel you don't
That's impossible
Hmm?
They're rank amateurs
Who don't even know how to use the trade shop
Don't make me laugh
In the trade shop
You can look at the official rankings of who has the most cards
Which can be really useful
And if you pay a fee
Then they'll even tell you which specific cards they have
But just because you can get a player's name from the ranking
Doesn't mean you can use contact or fluoroscopy
You gotta meet him for that
Do you feel a little smarter now?
Little boy?
Thing is, if we know all of the members on the team
We can determine exactly how many cards they have between them
And Team Genthrou is only missing
Numbers 0, 2, 9, and 75 in all
75, huh?
There's a well-accepted theory that number 0 only appears in an event
After the other 99 are collected
So they only need three
What we're proposing is this
We find one of those three types before they do and monopolize it
Preventing them from clearing the game
Really? That's it?
I figured we could at least inundate them with spell cards or something
We've learned that they already obtained a Paladin's necklace
So Levy is the only spell that might work
And they can block it
If certain conditions are met anyway
Let's assume that Genthrou is willing to reveal the fact that they have 96 types
Because they've got all their pages protected with Fortress
It's possible
And Genthrou was hoarding a bunch of spell cards
Him and the other guys who try to recruit us
So it makes a lot of sense
Well, we could always take their cards by force
Would you be willing to lead the attack?
Who knows what other abilities that three-man team has to offer?
The most practical plan is to find a card type to monopolize
No objections, I assume?
Then let's get down to business
We're gonna need everyone here working together
All that sounds good to me
But these new members are a problem
Hold on, Asta
Each team satisfies the prerequisite
All of them hold more than 50 cards
Just like you insisted to begin with
Yeah, maybe so
But I also insisted that they had to be people who could contribute, right?
I failed to see how either of these little kids are gonna contribute anything
The only one here not contributing so far is you
Well, at least you're a big talker
But I'm still not sure you can be useful
So let's see some proof
We know Team Gethrou's abilities
And there are three cards they're missing
We have one of them
Hmph, still got a problem?
That's good enough for me
So these abilities, what are they exactly?
Hold on
Let's see some proof that you can be useful to us
Because I doubt it
71 types of specified slot cards
That's a hell of a lot more than you have
How about I give you an A rank
In return for a little information
Is that good enough?
No, it isn't
We can get those ourselves
No big deal
If you want us to tell you anything
You can give us two S rank cards
Or equally valuable information
Don't press your luck, you damn little brat
Hear that, everyone?
These kids won't be any help
They want two S rank cards from each team
Ten cards
Really?
Don't be stupid
I just meant your team
Huh?
I'm fine giving information to the others
They can decide what they want to give us in return
But you?
You guys get nothing unless you give me what I asked for
Ugh
Shoulda known a stupid brat would dwell on that silly argument
Would both of you knock it off?
Don't waste our time fighting with each other
Well I haven't agreed to team up with them yet
Master, it's fine
Just give him two cards
He's right
We've got to move past this
Look, I don't have a problem with giving them cards
It doesn't make a difference to me
He's the one trying to pick a fight
No, you are picking a fight
Come on guys, let's get out of here
I don't want to team up with these losers
I know how you feel, it's frustrating
It's just that given the circumstances
Okay, what we've been able to figure out so far is that Genthru's abilities are Countdown and Little Flower
And that means that you're all going to want to keep a safe distance from him
Oh crap, bastard got me
Same here, back when we were making a deal
Me too
Seems to me like a bunch of them might be victims
Yeah
Is there a way to disable it?
Yup, sure is
You have to touch Genthru and say, I caught the bomber
Dummy, why'd you say that?
We could have milked a lot more cards out of them
Because it would have just started another fight
The bombs can't be armed until Genthru explains how his ability works to you
That's why, as long as you stay away from him, you should be fine
Did you boys know that there are two ways to cast your spells?
I did
A spell card is used up the moment you say the words and cast it
But there is a way you can keep reusing it
You know how a list of the players you've met appears?
As soon as you put a Pete card into your binder
Try this
Remove the card without pressing enter
You'll notice that the spell card isn't used up
So you can keep reusing it
I've never tried that, have you?
Nope
If you buy at the same trade shop over 50 times
Then you can buy all B-rank specified slot cards there
If you become a regular customer, they'll start bringing it up
Do you have a duplicate X-Ray Goggle card?
Beauty Magnet Emerald?
Maybe Wonder Pond?
So what do you think?
That satisfy you too?
Cause I'll give you another card if it doesn't
No, that's fine, thank you
Guess I'm up next then
Huh?
Garenu, very nice to meet you
That was fantastic, everybody
We learned lots from you guys, so thank you
The question now is which card we should try to monopolize
The number 75 we have is probably impossible
Each team can only get one of them
And the limit on that card is 20
That's way too high
You guys have a number 75?
That's really impressive
Now list on, number 75
Five other teams each have one
So a Monopoly is impossible
And the other two?
List on, number 9
And list on, number 2
No good
There are three teams that already have a number 9
But nobody has number 2, Strip of Beach yet
It just might work
Guidepost on, number 2
I know where to find it
Sofrabi
I've been there
I have an accompany card
All right, then let's go
Accompany on
To Sofrabi
So this is Sofrabi, huh?
It's a pretty big city
Let's head in and get info
We'll start at the edge and work inward
Some NPCs don't want to talk
So that's why you've got to visit them multiple times
Got it?
Yeah!
Hey!
Huh?
Seems they found someone with information
Backfast?
The pirates run this entire town
Every last inch of it
You see, there's this local legend
About an underwater cave called Poseidon's Cavern
That's supposed to be around here somewhere
The Strip of Beach is the entrance to it
Not too many years ago
Fifteen pirates came to this town
Because they'd heard about the legend
And that this cave also contained
An unbelievable amount of treasure inside
Razor and his 14 devils
The poor fishermen were all tortured and killed
Then the pirates murdered anybody
Who knew anything about the Strip of Beach
If you can get rid of the pirates
I promise I'll tell you everything I know
When we visited this place a few months ago
We couldn't find a single clue
Well, some info isn't always available
Maybe you can only get it this time of year?
Facing down Razor and his 14 devils, huh?
It's entirely possible that the event can only be triggered
By the right number of players
Huh?
There are 15 pirates
And it just so happens there are 15 of us
So what are you saying?
That the event won't start unless you have a party of 15 or more?
But I don't get it
How would an in-game character know about that?
With a company
Yes, 15 or more people must reach Sofrabi with a company
I'm willing to bet that that is the trigger for this event
Well, that's pretty brutal
What is?
Nothing
Right, to the pirates' base
Gohan and his friends encounter some unsavory-looking pirates
Their mission is clear
But will the 15 allies be able to obtain the strip of beach card?
You don't think so
We don't think so
Thank you
There's no voice
Back now
In the maiden
I don't think so
Do you
It's not abouthmm
Talking to theRadar
English
What are you saying?
Lucy
A
Hey
Let us
Is
ут
Whenever
Let hum
Come
Feed first
ıy
Until now...
Coming up, the Great Island Tutorial!